Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Yoshio Kishi's Files
  - Subseries B: Collected Articles
    - San Francisco's Anti-Chinese Ordinances 1850-1900, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - "In Search of Identity" by Bennet, Passin, and McKnight, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - "The Chinese in the United States of America" by Rose Hum Lee, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - "Mexican-American Labor Problems in Texas" by Lamar B. Jones, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Mixed collected articles, 1967, 1981, 1990's (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - TV Guide: Special Issue (with Lombardi article), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - "The Edwardians" by J.B. Priestly, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - The New York Post, 1971, 1976, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Proceedings of the Conference on Asian Gangs (photocopy), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1972, 1976, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - "Study of Japanese-Americans in Honolulu" by Yasumasa Kuroda, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "A Study of Japanese-Americans in Honolulu, Hawaii" by Tatsuzo Suzuki, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1973-1992, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "California Nativism" by Eldon R. Penrose, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "The Historiography of Japanese Americans: a Reevaluation" by Dennis S. Tachiki, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Tamking Chair Lectures, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Asian Americans: Annotated Bibliography, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Materials and Human Resources for Teaching Ethic Studies: An Annotated Bibliography, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - SI Films Box (1 of 4), 1978-1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - SI Films Box (2 of 4), 1975-1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - SI Films Box (3 of 4), 1976-1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - SI Films Box (4 of 4), 1981, 1987, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - "Gun in Check" by Bill Pronzini, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Info on Structure of Yamaguchi Gumi, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - International Examiner, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - The New York Nichibei, 1985, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - "Fred Houn: Artist and Activist" by Renne Renouf, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - "Japanese Warn of Repercussions from U.S. Move to Alter Jet Deal", Steven R. Weisman, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - "The Asian American Experience, Characteristics, and Fiction" by David R. Meyer, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence from Richard B. Iglehard, Chief Assistant Attorney General, California, re: People vs. Henderson, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - "A Long Musical March from China" by Mark Swed, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - The New York Times, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Newsweek, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "U.S. Companies in Japan Say Things Aren't So Bad" by David E. Sanger, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - "Five said to be Gang Members Plead Guilty to Armed Robberies" by James Barron, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - "Translators and Translations" by H.I. Inada, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Racism, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - M Business, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Mixed collected articles, 2000's (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Loose clippings, 2003, Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - CAAAV Voice, vol. 51, no.1, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Intelligence Report, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Library of Congress Information Bulletin, vol. 68, nos. 6, 11, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Mixed collected articles, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Mixed collected articles, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Mixed collected articles, 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - American Federation of Labor, Meat vs. Rice, Undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Boddy, Manchester, Undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - "Books for the Chinese-American Child: A selected list" by Cecilia Mei-Chen, Undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - A Chinese Night, Undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - "Close to Slavery: Guest Worker Programs in the United States", Undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Esquire (William Faulkner, Gore Vidal), Undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - "Filipino Firearms Smuggling", Undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Hideyo Noguchi, Undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - "Cut-Off Copple's" by Clarence King, Undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - L.A. County Sheriff's Dept - Murder of Henry Wong, Undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Lewis, Alfred Henry, Undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - "Little China in the City of Gold" by Margaret Loke, Undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Longstreet, Undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Mackey, Undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - McDonald scrapbook #4, Undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - McReynolds, George - "American Opinion on Japan", Undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Mixed collected articles, Undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - "Myopic Perceptions and Textbooks" by Albert H. Yee, Undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - "No Man's Land" by Christopher Rand, Undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Notehelfer, F.G. - "American Samurai", Undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - "Oriental Organized Crime in Australia", Undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Shaolin Hung-gar Kung Fu, Undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - "The Story of 'The Sun'" by Frank M. O'Brien, Undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Straight, Willard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - "The Theatre of New York's Chinatown" by Henry Tyrell, Undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Women of the Orient, Undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Wong, Jade Snow, Undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - IN Magazine [Flat Box], 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Life Magazine [Flat Box], 1964 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Life Magazine [Flat Box], 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Clippings on Japanese Films [Flat Box], 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Look Magazine [Flat Box], 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Look Magazine [Flat Box], 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - The Los Angeles Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1982 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1985, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1991, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1997-2007 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times Magazine [Flat Box], 2007 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Notes
    - Executive Order 9066: The Internment of 110,000 Japanese Americans - annotated with notes on Kishi's grandparents on page 29, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "Elementary Chinese for American Librarians" by John T. Ma, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Punch card - "Asian Studies Retreival Card", 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - S.F. Center, 1970, 1971, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - R & E Research Associates (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Iko, Momoko - correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - R & E Research Associates (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stengler, Albert - correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Asian American Film Festival, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - "Chinese Potpourri" autographed with note to Kishi written on paper towel, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1981, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Letter to the Editor - written by Kishi to the editor of the New York Nichibei, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Kazuhiko Kishi - correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - 1985 catalog of Asian Pacific American materials (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - A/A Center Bibliography, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - AMS Press (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - AMS Press (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Eastwind Books and Arts, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Harvard College Library Photographic Dept. Evidence, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dissertation Query, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Asian Cinevision, 1988, Undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Letters and invoices regarding acquiring books for the A/A Center of Queens College, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - South Asia Books (MO), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Shinwa Workers' Support Committee, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Yoshio Kishi notes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Emails to Kishi, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Field, R. Lance - Email correspondence, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Abadie poster E-Bay item, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Cameras, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - "45 different items on Asian American artists to be catalogued into...", Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Arno / Ayer, Undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - California: A Guide to the Golden State, annotated with Kishi's notes, Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Envelope printed in Japanese, Undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Footnotes for unknown writing, Undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Mixed writings, Undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Partial bibliographic outline, Undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - "Scrutable Contexts: Asian Threads in the American Fabric" speech and presentation delivered to the Library of Congress, Undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - The Valor of Ignorance (photocopy), Undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Subseries D: Collecting
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - AB Bookman's Weekly, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Allom, T. - Ebay receipt, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Alta California Bookstore, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Amerasia Resources, Asian Folklore and Social Life Monographs, Asian Rare Books, The Asia Society, 1964, 1971, 1972, 1989, 1992, Undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Antiquarium, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Arno Press, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Arkham House, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Asian American Experience, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Asian Rare Books, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Baird, Robert S; Best Books LTD; Bates, M. Woody; Black Sun Books; Blue Mountain Books and Manuscripts; Bloody Rare Books; Bloomsbury Book Auctions, 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bookman's Weekly; Books and Autographs; Bowling Green State Univerity Popular Press, 1984, 1990, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bloomsbury Auctions, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bolerium Books, 1988, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - "Book and Magazine Collector" no. 14, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - E.J. Brill, 1984, 1988, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - E.J. Brill, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Broadway Books, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Buddenbrooks, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Cheng and Tsui Co.; Cinemonde; Louis Collins Books; Curzon, 1985, 1990, 1991, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - California Book Auction Co., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - California Book Auction Co., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - California Book Auction Co., 1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - California Book Auction Co., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Christie's, 1980, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Christie's, 1988, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Coffee House Press, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - James Cummins Booksellers, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - CUNY, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Annie Davis, Movie Edition Books, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - George Eastman House, Simon Finch Rare Books, Golden Age of Movie Posters exhibition, 1956, 1985, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - cartoons, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - "Chinese Must Go" cap gun, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - CMLee Books, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Densmore, G.B., 2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Dime Novels, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Dime Novels and Penny Dreadfuls, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Eisenstein, Sergei, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Gulik, John Van, 1999, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Gulik, Robert Hans Van, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Gustave Dore illustration, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - eBay Receipts - Lane, Chei Mi, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Larry Edmonds Bookshop, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - A. Wilson Embrey, III, Undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Bill Epstein, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Fantasy Illustrated, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Films Incorporated 1978 Entertainment Catalog (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Firsts & Company, 1987, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Gregory C. Gamradt, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Gregory C. Gamradt, 1992, Undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Grapevine Flicks, 1985, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - "The Ground Glass", 1973 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Han Shan Tang, LTD; Het Ooster Antiquarium, 1990, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Heritage Bookshop, 1991, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Heritage Comics, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Inventory amounts - sold and unsold, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Kenneth Hince - Old and Fine Books, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Jenkins Company; Kenston Rare Books, Ralph Kristiansen, James & Mary Lowrie Booksellers, 1989, 1991, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Japan Old and New, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - JACP, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Jenkins Company, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Kinokuniya Publications book sales, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - M. Knoedler & Company, Inc, 1930-1931 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Limestone Hills Bookshop, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Movie Poster Service; Movie Star News; The Museum of Modern Art, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - McBlain Books, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - McBlain Books, 1989, 1990, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - McBlain Books, 1993, 1995, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - McBlain Books, 1997, 1999, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - McBlain Books, 2001, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Montreal Book Auctions, Ltd., 1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - W.M. Morrison Books, 1991, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Movies Unlimited Video Catalog, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Murray Summers, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Music catalogs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - The Nineteenth Century Shop; Nelson's Bookroom, 1990, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - NYC, 1988, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Oriental Art References; Oriental Lost Art & Rare Book Co., 1989, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Paper Collector's Marketplace; Phillip J. Pirages; Nicholas Pounder Bookseller; Paradox Gallery, 1978, 1988, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Paragon Book Gallery, Illinois, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Paragon Book Gallery, Ltd, 1988-1991 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Fong Plummer Associates, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Polyanthos Park Avenue Books, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Larry E. Price Books, 1988, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Quality First; Randall House; Rare and Unusual Americana; Robert Frost Books; Cedric L. Robinson Booksellers, 1979, 1983, 1990, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1988, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1991, Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Reese Company, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - R.N. Reynolds, 1983, 1988, Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - George G. Rinhart, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - George G. Rinhart, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - George G. Rinhart, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Paul A. Riseman, 1991-1992, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Duane Robeck, Bookseller, 1994, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - William Salloch; Serendipity Books; Shakespeare et al; Swann Galleries, 1989, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyer's Books, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyer's Books, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyer's Books, 1992, 1994, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyler's Books, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyer's Books, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Schoyer's Books, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Second Life Books, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Shanghai Express, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Sotheby's, 1976, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Sotheby's, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Sotheby's, 1980, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Sotheby's, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Jerrold G. Stanhoff, 1973-1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Jerrold G. Stanhoff, 1973-1975, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Sumner & Stillman, 1990, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Augustine Tam Books; Tuttle Antiquarian Books; Jon C. Van Doren, 1984, 1992, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Terramedia Books, 1989, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - University of Hawaii Press, 1983, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Edna Whiteson A.B.A.; Willis Monie Books; Witkin; Wittenborn Art Books Inc; Words Etcetera, 1975, 1989, 1990, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Weekend Gallery Books / The Old Bookroom, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Nigel Williams Books, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Charles B. Wood, III, Inc., 1991, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Ruth Woods Oriental Books and Art, 1988-1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Worldwide Antiquarian, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Worldwide Antiquarian, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Worldwide Antiquarian, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Catalogs and Price Lists - Worldwide Antiquarian, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Guides - Academy Award Winner's Movie Posters, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Guides - An American Postcards Collector's Guide, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Guides - Asian American Studies collections, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Guides - Asian Americana collections checklist, Undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Guides - Attack of the "B" Movie Posters, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Guides - Best Pictures' Movie Posters, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Guides - Collecting Picture Postcards - an Introduction, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Guides - Collecting Postcards in Colour 1914-1930, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Guides - The Collector's Guide to Post Cards, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Guides - Collector's Guide to Treasures from the Silver Screen, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Guides - Joe Franklin's Showbiz Memorabilia, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Guides - More Cowboy Movie Posters, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Guides - The Movie Poster Book, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Guides - Not Nominated Movie Posters, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Guides - Photography Directory and Buying guide, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Guides - Photography: The Early Years - A Historical Guide for Collectors, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Guides - Portfolio of Photographica, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Guides - Pioneer Postcards, Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Guides - Postcard Companion: The Collector's References, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Guides - Posters (eMoviePoster.com), 2004 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - Antiquarian Book Fair and Paper Show Directory, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - "China Tourism" Subjuct Index for Issues 1-90, Undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - Chinese American Tokens, by R.F. Merberg - photocopy, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - Dashell Hammett Tour, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - "Mag-a-Book" vol. 1, no. 23, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - The Murder Book: An Illustrated History of the Detective Story", 1971 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - The Museum of Modern Art: Printing and Sculpture Acquisitions, 1957, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 28)